[theme music playing]
Only I have the right
to discipline Arnaldo.
But how did he turn out?!
He's no different than you!
He's a criminal now!
-Kill this insolent bastard!
-Papa! Papa, don't!
Get out of here, Raul. Leave.
[Arnaldo] I haven't killed
anyone aside from Nimfa.
Wait, if you release this, that means…
That's the only way
I can think of to help Diego
and put a stop to Arnaldo's ruthlessness.
Lily's coming back,
so they better watch out.
I feel Ivy is keeping
her true relationship
with Diego a secret.
Test her. Use Diego.
[Diego] Fight me fair and square.
[Arnaldo] Fight? I'm finishing
you off right here.
[Arnaldo grunts]
Diego! Stop it!
This isn't over.
I'd like to propose something.
Let's do a pre-election survey.
Whoever wins there is the one
who's telling the truth.
Now, who are they going to choose?
A criminal,
or an honest politician like me?
Let them decide.
[Raul] Gather all our men.
And round up every judge in Ardiente.
I am not going to reshape
Ardiente. You are.
If you really love our province,
you'll choose what is right.
You will choose change.
[Natalie] Who did Emilia ask you to find?
Miss Lily Cruz.
Lily Cruz, huh?
That's impossible!
Diego beat me?! I don't believe it!
How did this dog beat you?!
Well?
Auntie.
-[Camia] Diego.
-Attorney.
DIEGO TORILLO SECURES
LANDSLIDE SURVEY WIN
[Camia chuckles]
Diego, you got 82%!
That means the people
of Ardiente have faith in you!
That's why, as early as now,
I'm confident you're going to
win the election.
-Auntie!
-[Camia chuckles]
And I have another good news for you.
-Sit down, please.
-Judge De Jesus is back…
And she withdrew from your case.
A new judge is handling this now.
It's Judge Rotico
from the neighboring province.
We've got a high chance
of winning this case, Diego.
[Camia] Diego.
[Camia] Thank you, Attorney.
Thank you so much, Attorney!
[tense music playing]
DIEGO TORILLO SECURES
LANDSLIDE SURVEY WIN
[Raul] Rufo!
Yes, Jaguar?
Have our men guard Diego in jail.
I'm sure the Ardientes aren't happy
about the results of the survey.
I'll get right to it, Jaguar.
If things get out of hand,
you know what to do.
Break Diego out…
and bring him here.
[tense music playing]
This sucks!
[frustrated] Eighty-two percent?!
That's a humongous number!
That basically ensures Diego's
victory in this election!
No! That's not gonna happen!
I'm going to win.
-Me!
-Of course, you are.
We Ardientes are the rightful
leaders of this town.
That is why…
we're going to have Diego killed.
[tense music playing]
Hello.
Finish off Diego Torillo.
Done.
[ominous music playing]
[jail cell opening]
[sinister music playing]
[action music playing]
[goon shouts]
[tense music playing]
[screams in pain]
-Think you're so tough?!
-Fight back!
[goon shouting] Show us what you got!
[goon laughing]
Fight back! Get up!
Get him!
[action music playing]
[goon] You got spunk! Get up!
[goon cackling]
What now? Kneel!
-[laughter]
-I said kneel!
-Come on! Get up!
-Get up!
-Stubborn, eh?
-You aren't so tough now!
[grunting]
[goons cackling]
[goons jeering]
What?!
Going to fight back?
[tense music playing]
[goon] More!
[goon cackling]
So, what's it going to be?
[goon laughing]
I thought he was tough.
Why don't you cry?
So?
Dude, finish him. Congressman's orders.
[tense music playing]
Ivy, where are you going?
Oh, just some matters to attend to. Work.
Would you rather put work first
than console my son on his defeat?
Well, Emilia, I already spoke
to Arnaldo. He understands me.
And I'm sure you know
how important work is.
[Emilia sighs]
Yes, you're right, Ivy.
But why don't you come with me?
Why don't you accompany me?
Whatever it is, I'm sorry,
I'm not interested.
Are you sure?
Even if it's about Lily Cruz?
You see, Ivy…
I've long been looking for Lily Cruz.
All my hard work paid off!
I'll finally meet her.
And I also want you to meet her.
You know,
you might have a lot of things
in common with each other.
Congrats! Finally!
You'll finally meet Lily Cruz!
The person Emilia fears the most.
-Me? Afraid of Lily Cruz?
-Yes!
Don't you remember? You passed out.
But don't worry, future mother-in-law.
I always carry some ammonia
in case you pass out again.
[both giggling]
You know, Ivy, we really love
mocking each other, right?
[sighs] But you see,
I want you to come along
because I want you to witness
how I become a ruthless bitch.
Because this time,
I will…
kill Lily Cruz myself.
Bang! Bang! Bang!
[laughs]
Three!
Straight in the heart! It's like saying…
"Die, bitch! Die, bitch!
I hate you, bitch!"
Hey. Are you scared? You look pale.
It's as if you're saying
that you're Lily Cruz!
Oh, Ivy. Didn't I tell you?
I got your back.
Chill! Relax.
The end is near.
Come!
[tense music playing]
You want to chill?
I'll help you.
[goon] Dude, finish him.
[tense music playing]
[goon shouting]
[Diego screaming in pain]
[goons laughing]
You got him!
[goons jeering]
He's a bastard.
[tense music playing]
Don't try anything else on my son…
or I'll kill you, Julio Ardiente.
[action music playing]
Hey!
Get away from him.
[man shouting]
Diego!
Let's get out of here!
Come on!
[Diego] Wait! Wait!
Come on! Come on!
No! Who are you?
We're Jaguar's men. Let's go!
-Who's Jaguar?
-Let's go! Let's go!
-Who's Jaguar?!
-You'll find out soon enough.
Let's go!
Diego, you're going to die
if you stay here!
Do you understand?! Come on!
Let's go.
I don't care! I'm not going with you!
You really are stubborn.
Jaguar was right.
Let's go, Diego! Come on!
-I'm not going with you!
-Quit it! Come with us!
-I don't need to escape!
-Hurry!
-I'm innocent!
-Come with us! Hurry!
I'm not going with you!
Come on! Let's get out of here!
Wait. Wait! Who's Jaguar?!
Wait!
[action music continues]
Over here!
Get them up.
Come on!
Get up! Get up!
-[Diego] Wait, I'm injured.
-Get up!
-Take him.
-Wait.
Go on. Hurry.
Finally, it's over.
Diego is done for.
My problem is solved.
Our problem, Grandpa.
No one can block my candidacy.
And the result
of the survey? It's useless.
Good as null and void.
On top of that, no one can
bother me and Ivy anymore.
Well, a fitting fairy-tale ending
for both of you.
That's why we deserve
this prime rib that we're partaking.
-Eat up, boy.
-That's right.
Oh, by the way, Grandpa, I'm just curious
because I've been meaning to ask you
this for a long time already.
Why did you even raise Diego?
Come on, you sent him to school
and gave him the name Ardiente.
He was already a bad investment
from the start
since you knew he was
my dad's illegitimate child.
It was all because of your mother.
Your mother and her blind,
dumb, stupid love for your father, Raul.
Okay, that made sense.
What if Dad brainwashes Mom again…
and asks her to have Diego released?
That would be too late…
because even as we're
having dinner and speaking,
Diego may be taking in his last breath.
[Julio chuckles]
Here's to your victory
as the future leader
of the Ardiente clan.
Cheers to that.
[moans]
[bleak music playing]
Are you sure she's here?
Yes, ma'am. Let's go inside.
Emilia, wait.
This feels off.
[sighs]
I have a bad feeling about this.
Let's go home.
Oh, come on! It's too late to back out.
Don't be a party pooper!
Lily's waiting. Hurry up.
No! We have to go home. Let's go.
We won't. You will come with me inside…
because I'll use you as a human shield,
just in case Lily Cruz has a gun.
Let's get going. Let's go in.
-Emilia, listen to me!
-Come on, we're here already.
Hurry up.
[ominous music playing]
Lily!
Lily Cruz!
Lily Cruz, where are you?
Emilia, let's go.
To be honest, I don't trust that
private investigator of yours.
Can you just shut up?
Lily Cruz! Where are you?
I'm getting impatient!
I have something for you! A coffin!
Aren't you excited?
[frustrated] Lily Cruz! Show yourself!
I can't wait any longer!
You're getting on my nerves!
Lily!
[suspenseful music playing]
[hushed tone] Emilia. I told you.
[gunshots]
[bullets buzzing]
[Emilia screams]
Emilia, hide!
[Ivy grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
I told you, Emilia! I told you!
[groans]
If you only listened to me!
[sinister music playing]
[laughing]
Natalie?!
[exhales] Did you pee
in your pants, Emilia?
[Natalie laughing]
Yes! It's me!
And I'm back… in the flesh!
[tense music playing]
You're Lily Cruz?!
[Natalie laughing]
Lily who?!
I don't know who that is.
I just took advantage
of your obsession with finding her
because I'm dying to see you.
[Natalie chuckles]
And I didn't expect that woman
to be here tonight too.
Miss Ivy "Snake" Aguas.
The bitch who stole
the love of my life, Arnaldo.
[laughing]
As far as I'm concerned,
you and Arnaldo are over, Natalie.
I know, right?!
[sighs] My goodness, finally!
But, you and me? We aren't done yet.
You go to hell, you bitch!
Oops!
I'll see you there!
What's your problem, Natalie?
My poor daddy!
He trusted you!
But you had him murdered!
[Natalie breathing heavily]
That's why I'm here.
Because it's payback time, Emilia!
[tense music playing]
I'm going to make you suffer
before you die.
[tense music playing]
[gunshot]
-[Emilia exclaims]
-Emilia!
Split them up!
I'll deal with these bitches separately.
[Emilia] No! Don't do this, Natalie!
If you want to kill someone, kill her!
Kill her, and I promise you…
-Oh.
-you'll have Arnaldo back!
-Seriously, Emilia? Wow!
-[Natalie laughs]
[Natalie sighs]
Emilia, I've finally moved on.
And you might lose it when
I tell you who my new man is!
[tense music playing]
[Natalie laughs hysterically]
[whoops]
-[laughing]
-[goons] Let's go!
-Let's go!
-Move!
-Don't touch me! Let go!
Don't touch me!
-[goon] Stop resisting.
-What the--
-Ouch!
-[Julio] I wonder…
where your mother and Ivy could be.
Ivy didn't tell me
where they were going either.
As a matter of fact,
she hasn't replied
to any of my text messages.
[ominous music playing]
It's either of two things.
They went out shopping,
or they've done something
foolish like kill each other.
You know, I used to find it
amusing, but not anymore.
Don't say that, Grandpa.
I want them to get along, okay?
[Julio chuckles]
Never! That's never going
to happen, Arnaldo.
You put two bullies in one room,
and there's going to be bloodshed.
Come to think of it, you know,
you were better off
with that Natalie woman.
[Arnaldo scoffs]
At least, she and your mother got along.
If only Emilia hadn't had Pablo killed.
Things would've been a lot easier for us.
Well, good thing I don't like it easy.
Okay? I like Ivy because
she challenges me.
She weakens you!
You factor her into
every decision you make!
Do I really have to say it again?
I love her, okay? I love her.
Plain and simple.
And how about Ivy?
Does she truly love you?
Huh?
[tense music playing]
-She does. I know she loves me.
-[scoffs]
Well, well, well… We'll see.
Let's see how she'll react when
she finds out that Diego's dead.
Congressman, you have a visitor.
I believe you have good news for me?
Bad news, Congressman…
Jaguar's men broke into
the station and rescued Diego
from the hands of our men.
Fine. You may go. Go!
Bunch of nincompoops!
[Diego groaning]
[tense music playing]
[groaning]
[breathing heavily]
Jaguar.
Who are you, Jaguar?
Why are you helping me?
Are you also an enemy of the Ardientes?
I know…
I know they're responsible for this.
The minute I get out of here,
I'll make them pay.
They'll all pay.
Well? How did it go? Where's Diego?
As expected, the Ardientes
wanted to have him killed.
It's a good thing we got there.
Otherwise, he'd be dead by now.
Didn't I tell you to get him out of there?
Jaguar, he refused to come. He says he's
innocent, so he doesn't need to escape.
That stubborn kid
still puts his principles first.
[sighs]
Fine. Let's get ready.
Why, Jaguar?
It's time for Diego and I to work together
and take the Ardientes down.
[ominous music playing]
-Is everything ready?
-Yes, doc.
Good.
[Diego groans]
Sir…
[soft piano music playing]
[groans]
We need to clean and treat your wounds.
Nurse, have a portable
X-ray machine sent here
to make sure that the patient is
not suffering from any bone fractures.
-Okay?
-Yes, doc. Excuse me.
Have a seat.
-Careful. Relax.
-[Diego groans]
After I treat your wounds,
you can eat and get some rest.
Tell Jaguar that I don't need his help.
Wait.
[brooding music playing]
He wants to talk to you.
[tense music playing]
[Loring] Oh, Ma'am Camia.
I have a bad feeling about
that judge's disappearance.
What did you say, Loring? The judge…
-Yes.
-[Pandoy] She's missing?
Those damned Ardientes
will do everything to win!
Yes, and I'm worried about Diego's case!
Mr. Pandoy, Miss Loring, please calm down.
Ma'am, it's just…
It's hard to stay calm when you
know your child is in danger.
[soft music playing]
I know how you feel, Miss Loring.
But, we must stay strong.
We have to believe
that Diego will get past this.
Ma'am, I know that.
I believe that Diego can handle this.
I just don't want him to get hurt.
All his life, he's faced nothing
but pain from the Ardientes.
Now, I just want him to be happy.
Please have faith.
Diego will soon be free.
Diego will be free from the Ardientes.
[somber music playing]
[ominous music playing]
What do you want from me?
Why are you helping me?
No. This is not good.
Okay?
Jaguar is now Diego's protector
and supporter.
He's now a legitimate threat.
That he is.
And that means
the fight will only get tougher.
But…
We are Ardientes.
We've been through
a lot of battles and wars.
As the battle draws out longer,
the fiercer we become.
If they're looking for a good fight,
we'll give them one.
Been there, done that.
[sinister music playing]
Jaguar says, given your situation,
you're the one who needs him.
He's going to help you run for governor…
by providing you with money,
personnel, and weapons.
And, Diego,
he also guarantees your victory
in your fight against Arnaldo.
First of all, I don't trust
anyone who hides their face…
and doesn't choose to talk.
Second, I don't need your dirty money.
Lastly…
I'll defeat the Ardientes
using the force of the masses.
What I want is change for Ardiente,
not to replace a demon with another demon.
[tense music playing]
So… How do you want to go, Emilia?
Do you want to get shot
and die right away?
Or do you want it to be long and painful?
Do you want to suffer before you die?
Have you decided yet?
Or…
Better yet…
[tense music playing]
Should I flay you alive
and pour acid on you?
Then, I'll burn you to death.
Isn't that a grand entrance to hell?
How do you like that?
Are you sure you want
to end things this way?
I'm warning you, Natalie.
[tense music playing]
I need to get out of here.
[ominous music playing]
You don't call the shots anymore!
I do.
That one's for my dad.
[mocking tone] More.
And that one's for the wound in his chest.
[ominous music playing]
[Natalie grunting]
Are you done? Then, it's my turn.
Go reunite with your father in hell!
[goons] Ma'am! Ma'am! Ma'am! Ma'am!
Sit down, bitch.
That's right.
I won't let you go until you die, Emilia.
You murdered my father.
So I have to do the same to you.
That's right, bitch. Sit down.
[tense music playing]
Boys.
[foreboding music playing]
The next time this woman tries to escape…
I'll shoot every bullet
in this gun into your brains!
You got it?
Don't be stupid!
Understand?!
Your son really is stubborn.
Let's see how much he can take.
I know Diego. I'm his dad.
If his loved ones are in danger…
he'll have no choice but to give in.
He'll bite the bullet.
Jaguar, can you do that to your own son?
If that's what it takes
to make him win against Arnaldo, why not?
Now, where was I?
Oh yeah. You know what?
Even if we both have our differences,
I still have a heart.
That's why I'm giving you a chance
to talk to someone very special.
And the question is,
who could it be?!
[suspenseful music]
Letter A, is it your father, Julio?
Or letter B,
your son, Mayor Arnaldo?
Or letter C…
your beloved husband, Raul?
I wonder…
Why do I have his number?
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-Hello, Raul.
Emilia?
Save me because Natalie
is going to kill me.
Save me now!
[laughing]
Emilia. Hello?
Hi, Raul!
[giggles] Did you miss me?
Did you hear what your wife said?
She said…
you should save her from me!
Natalie, what are you gonna do to Emilia?!
Natalie, don't hurt her!
Natalie?! Hello! Natalie!
[tense music playing]
Rufo, we have a problem.
Natalie has taken Emilia!
Don't let her hurt Emilia!
[grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[sighs]
For some reason, your husband
told me not to kill you.
Now, why would I listen to him?
Why should I do what he says?
It's not as if I'm sleeping
with your husband.
Oh, yeah! [chuckles] I am!
[Natalie laughs]
My husband would never sleep with you.
You sure about that, Emilia?
[Natalie laughing]
I wouldn't say so.
You know what? You're looking at me.
And you know I'm sexy.
You, of all people, know…
-that men love me.
-You aren't his type!
I know my husband better.
He wouldn't go after
some cheap slut like you!
Cheap?
Me?! [laughs]
Don't worry about that.
When you die,
I'll look after your husband.
And guess what? I'm gonna
take good care of him.
Who are you calling "cheap" again?
Is it me or you?
[action music playing]
[Ivy grunting]
My husband loves me.
He even promised me
he wouldn't hurt me again.
I'm sure you're just telling me
that to hurt me!
-You're a liar!
-[laughs]
You know that I'm not a liar!
We were friends before. You know that.
[sighs heavily] Did I hurt you?
Yeah.
I pity you, Emilia. You're miserable.
Raul, for some reason, is your life.
No matter what he does,
even if he cheats on you,
you will always be there for him.
But it doesn't matter anymore
because you'll die soon.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia chuckling]
Find it funny?
My husband loves me.
How about you?
You're just a wet pillow.
[ominous music playing]
[somber music playing]
[jail cell opening]
[cell door squeaking]
[tense music playing]
Right here.
I've prepared this spot
just for you, Emilia.
You know…
I've been waiting for this moment.
What were you saying again?
Raul loves you?
Are you sure about that?
[ominous music playing]
Because the only thing
that's in love with you right now…
is my little friend.
I've waited for this moment, Emilia.
[sniffles]
[exhales]
[tense music playing]
This feels really good right now.
There's a grand reunion just for you.
Bye, Emilia.
[tense music playing]
You do deserve this for
everything you've done, Emilia.
[tense music playing]
-[Natalie shouts]
-[gunshot]
What's wrong with you?!
Jaguar?!
Keep an eye on her!
[tense music playing]
[action music playing]
Ivy!
I was supposed to leave you to die here
because you wanted Natalie to kill me.
But then, I'd never do that
to Arnaldo. He might assume
that I let my future
mother-in-law die here.
[Emilia sobbing]
Ivy, thank you.
This isn't how I envisioned
your death, Emilia.
Ivy, thank you!
[scoffs]
Don't thank me just yet.
We need to get out of here first.
-Run, Emilia!
-Ivy, wait!
Do you want to die? Hurry up!
-Come here.
-Let go of me!
Natalie, what do you think you're doing?!
Have you forgotten already?
She killed my father!
Of course, I have to avenge him.
I know all that,
but we can still use Emilia!
For what?!
Tell me!
I had Emilia's wake scheduled
today so I have to kill her!
No one can stop me! Not even you!
Don't you ever test me.
I don't want my plans ruined.
So you better release Emilia!
[tense music playing]
-[sighs]
-[somber music playing]
[voice prompt] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
Lily, you haven't contacted me
for almost a day.
Where on earth are you?
[Arnaldo] You know what, Grandpa?
I was just thinking.
What if…
my dad is the Jaguar?
[laughing]
What?
That is the most
ridiculous thing I can think of.
Your father is poorer than a rat.
I mean, he still has to ask me
for money to buy underwear.
And you would think that
he can be someone like Jaguar?
[laughing]
But this Jaguar…
I'm certain he's rich.
And I have a feeling that he's connected
to a lot of powerful people.
I really wonder who he is.
Why--
Why has he only appeared now?
[phone ringing]
[Julio chuckles]
-Oh!
-[phone ringing]
Speak of the devil.
It's your dad, the rodent.
Hello, Raul.
Yes, Papa.
This better be worth my time, or else…
Papa, Emilia called me asking for help.
She and Ivy were kidnapped.
She said they were going to be killed.
What?!
That bastard Jaguar is really
making my blood boil!
He's obviously challenging me!
Why? What happened?
He kidnapped your mother and Ivy.
What?! We have to save them!
Hello, Dad. What did Mom say?
How's Ivy? Is she hurt?
I don't know, son.
The line got disconnected.
How about this, Arnaldo?
Let's help each other look for them.
Jaguar is really getting on my nerves.
[tense music playing]
[Camia] Even though Diego's in prison,
we can beat them together.
[Emilia] We should look for a place
without trash lying around.
You're garbage!
Shut up!
You won't be able to salvage
your tarnished reputation.
Because we will win this election!
Is he working with Jaguar?
if they continue to work
together, I might lose.
"Call me, my beautiful."
Jaguar's quite the sweet-talker, isn't he?
-Just like Raul?
-If you really want me,
then show yourself.
You can't hide under your mask forever.
[Jaguar] I have one condition.
I want it to be just the two of us.
No one else.
[theme music playing]